Family for Christmas is a family, romance, tv movie
film directed by Amanda Tapping.
At the height of her career, investigative journalist Hannah Dunbar finds herself wondering what
would have been had she stayed with the love of her life, Ben, 10 years before.
When Santa Claus hears her “what ifs?” as a Christmas wish, he transports
Hannah to a version of her life where she and Ben started a family.
Hannah Dunbar, played by Lacey Chabert.
Ben Matthews, played by Tyron Leitso.
Grant Walker, played by Matthew Kevin Anderson.
Carrie Garrett, played by Brittney Wilson.
Tammy Frink, played by Jill Morrison.
Santa Clause, played by Keith MacKechnie.
Almost Christmas is a 2016 American Christmas
comedy-drama film written and directed by David E.
Talbert and starring Kimberly Elise, Mo'Nique, Nicole Ari Parker, Gabrielle Union, Keri
Hilson, Jessie Usher, Danny Glover, Omar Epps, John Michael Higgins, D.C.
Young Fly, and Romany Malco.
The film follows a dysfunctional family that comes together for the
holidays for the first time since their mother's death.
Principal photography took place during November and
December 2015 in Covington, Georgia.
The film premiered in Los Angeles on November 3, 2016 and was theatrically released
in the United States on November 11, 2016 by Universal Pictures.
It received mixed reviews and grossed $42 million.
The tone is emotional.